reliablesite.net 2013-11-26

# Privacy Policy :: ReliableSite.Net LLC

Introduction  
ReliableSite.Net maintains this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. As part of our normal operations, we collect and, in some instances, disclose information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. ReliableSite.Net reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. You agree that any changes will be effective when posted on-line at this location and that your continued use of ReliableSite.Net LLC's Services will constitute your acceptance of any changes or additions to this Privacy Policy. You may identify whether ReliableSite.Net has revised this Privacy Policy by noting the "Effective Date" below. 

When you order web hosting services ("Services") from us, you are required to provide certain personal information to us to allow us to process your order, start providing you with the Services you order from us, and to administer and service your account and provide ongoing technical support. The information you provide to us and that we maintain in our customer account records ranges from basic contact information, to credit card and other payment information, to technical information about your web site. You must provide all of the information we request from you when purchasing our Services. When you purchase our Services, you agree to provide and maintain accurate, complete and updated information. 

After you have signed up for our Services, we may be in communication with you about your account, technical questions you may have about the Services, or any other matter relating to the Services. These communications are essential to our relationship with you and to our ability to provide you with quality Services that are responsive to your needs. As a result, we may maintain information about our communications with you for future use. 

We may use cookies to keep track of your use of our Services. Cookies are small text files that are sent to your browser and stored on your computer. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to recognize you when you visit our Services. 

Our Disclosure of Your Information  
We will not use your information for internal secondary uses (i.e., uses that do not directly relate to your ordering or ongoing use of our Services), or share your information with any third parties. In the event that this policy changes, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit the secondary use of your information or the disclosure of your information to third parties. We will never willfully sell, lease, or rent any personally identifiable information about you or your business to any third party without first receiving your permission. 

We cannot ensure that all of your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be required to disclose personally identifiable information to the government or by court order under certain circumstances. In addition, you authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole and exclusive discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. 

Security  
In order to maximize protection of your information, we use state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from improper use or disclosure, unauthorized access, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all of your personal information, including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted over the Internet. Of course, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure, and we do not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data on or through the use of our Services is at your own risk. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other sites. All of our employees and contractors who have access to, and are associated with the processing of your information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your personal data. 

Corrections & Changes  
You have the ability to correct or change certain information in our records, such as your address and contact information. You may change this information at any time and as often as necessary. If you need assistance or have questions about correcting information, you may contact us via e-mail at support@reliablesite.net . 

General  
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Service that you accept when ordering our Services. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy protection practices, please contact us at support@reliablesite.net . 

Effective Date  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 31st, 2006.
